peterlbrandt.com 2019-05-12

# Privacy Policy | Peter Brandt - Factor Trading

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Updated: April 1, 2016

This Privacy is governed by our Terms of Use (<http://www.peterlbrandt.com/termsofuse/>) and is incorporated therein by reference. If there is a conflict between our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, the Terms of Use shall govern.

**Gathering of Information**

One of our goals in collecting member information is to enhance your experience when using our Services, such as tailoring the content you receive based on which areas of our website you visit. For example, we do not track what you read, but instead how well each page or content area performs overall based on member visits.

We are committed to protecting your privacy, and know you too are vested in having your privacy protected. Therefore, you should be aware that we collect the following information about you when you use our website and Services.

_Personal Information_

We automatically collect information about your IP address, browser type, where your visit originated and your device type. This information is collected in a database and used — in an aggregated, anonymous manner — for our internal analysis of traffic patterns within our website.

In addition, we may request that you provide personal information when you become a registered member, so we can improve our Services. Although you may have the option to opt out of providing this additional information, in some instances by not providing an answer will be unable to access certain Services. This information is used for internal Service development purposes only.

_Browser Level Information — Cookies_

A cookie is a data file that certain websites write to your computer’s hard drive when you visit such sites. A cookie file can contain information, such as a user identification code that the site uses to track the pages you have visited. We use cookies solely to track your traffic patterns throughout our website. We use this data on an anonymous basis and do not correlate this information with your personal information. The acceptance of cookies allows you to have a more streamlined and enhanced navigation experience.

Most website browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser settings to display a warning before accepting a cookie, or to refuse all cookies. However if you choose to disable the receipt of cookies from our website, you may not be able to use certain Services.

**Use of Information**

All information we collect is used to validate usernames and passwords, improve our Services, or offer you our Services. We do not sell our member’s information or share it with third parties except when required by law or in emergency or extenuating circumstances.

Please be aware, however, that advertisers or other websites that have links on our website may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of these third parties and websites are not covered by our Privacy Policy.

Please also be aware that if you choose to disclose personal information in public areas of our Services (e.g. chat areas or bulletin boards) that information may be collected by others and may result in unsolicited contact from others.

We may change our Privacy Policy, in our sole discretion, from time to time, so please check back periodically to view any changes or updates.
